<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="funny_quotes">
        <item>Always remember that you are absolutely unique. Just like everyone else.[Margaret Mead]</item>
        <item>People who think they know everything are a great annoyance to those of us who do.[Isaac Asimov]</item>
        <item>Get your facts first, then you can distort them as you please.[Mark Twain]</item>
        <item>A woman\'s mind is cleaner than a man\'s: She changes it more often.[Oliver Herford]</item>
        <item>A day without sunshine is like, you know, night.[Steve Martin]</item>
        <item>I may be drunk, Miss, but in the morning I will be sober and you will still be ugly.[Winston Churchill]</item>
        <item>A successful man is one who makes more money than his wife can spend. A successful woman is one who can find such a man.[Lana Turner]</item>
        <item>Weather forecast for tonight: dark.[George Carlin]</item>
        <item>Roses are red, violets are blue, I\'m schizophrenic, and so am I.[Oscar Levant]</item>
        <item>My fake plants died because I did not pretend to water them.[Mitch Hedberg]</item>
        <item>It takes considerable knowledge just to realize the extent of your own ignorance.[Thomas Sowell</item>
        <item>The trouble with having an open mind, of course, is that people will insist on coming along and trying to put things in it.[Terry
            Pratchett]</item>
        <item>All generalizations are false, including this one.[Mark Twain]</item>
        <item>Prejudice is a great time saver. You can form opinions without having to get the facts.[E. B. White]</item>
        <item>They say marriages are made in Heaven. But so is thunder and lightning.[Clint Eastwood]</item>
        <item>No man has a good enough memory to be a successful liar.[Abraham Lincoln]</item>
        <item>I always wanted to be somebody, but now I realize I should have been more specific.[Lily Tomlin]</item>
        <item>Before I refuse to take your questions, I have an opening statement.[Ronald Reagan]</item>
        <item>The chief function of the body is to carry the brain around.[Thomas A. Edison]</item>
        <item>Do not worry about avoiding temptation. As you grow older it will avoid you.[Joey Adams]</item>
        <item>Life is hard. After all, it kills you.[Katharine Hepburn]</item>
        <item>Everything I like is either illegal, immoral or fattening.[Alexander Woollcott]</item>
        <item>Society is like a stew. If you don\'t stir it up every once in a while then a layer of scum floats to the top.[Edward Abbey]</item>
        <item>I cook with wine, sometimes I even add it to the food.[W. C. Fields]</item>
        <item>Common sense is the collection of prejudices acquired by age eighteen.[Albert Einstein]</item>
        <item>I like long walks, especially when they are taken by people who annoy me.[Fred Allen]</item>
        <item>We owe a lot to Thomas Edison - if it wasn\'t for him, we\'d be watching television by candlelight.[Milton Berle]</item>
        <item>Never put a sock in a toaster.[Eddie Izzard]</item>
        <item>I would like to die on Mars. Just not on impact.[Elon Musk]</item>
        <item>I have a memory like an elephant. I remember every elephant I\'ve ever met.[Herb Caen]</item>
        <item>TV is chewing gum for the eyes.[Frank Lloyd Wright]</item>
        <item>I can speak Esperanto like a native.[Spike Milligan]</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="smart_quotes">
        <item>Life is about making an impact, not making an income.[Kevin Kruse]</item>
        <item>Whatever the mind of man can conceive and believe, it can achieve.[Napoleon Hill]</item>
        <item>Strive not to be a success, but rather to be of value.[Albert Einstein]</item>
        <item>You miss 100% of the shots you don\'t take.[Wayne Gretzky]</item>
        <item>Life is what happens to you while you\'re busy making other plans.[John Lennon]</item>
        <item>We become what we think about.[Earl Nightingale]</item>
        <item>Life is 10% what happens to me and 90% of how I react to it.[Charles Swindoll]</item>
        <item>The mind is everything. What you think you become.[Buddha]</item>
        <item>The best time to plant a tree was 20 years ago. The second best time is now.[Chinese Proverb]</item>
        <item>An unexamined life is not worth living.[Socrates]</item>
        <item>Your time is limited, so don\'t waste it living someone else\'s life.[Steve Jobs]</item>
        <item>I am not a product of my circumstances. I am a product of my decisions.[Stephen Covey]</item>
        <item>Every child is an artist.  The problem is how to remain an artist once he grows up.[Pablo Picasso]</item>
        <item>You can never cross the ocean until you have the courage to lose sight of the shore.[Christopher Columbus]</item>
        <item>I\'ve learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel.[Maya
            Angelou]</item>
        <item>Whether you think you can or you think you can\'t, you\'re right.[Henry Ford]</item>
        <item>The best revenge is massive success.[Frank Sinatra]</item>
        <item>People often say that motivation doesn\'t last. Well, neither does bathing.  That\'s why we recommend it daily.[Zig Ziglar]</item>
        <item>Life shrinks or expands in proportion to one\'s courage.[Anais Nin]</item>
        <item>If you hear a voice within you say “you cannot paint,” then by all means paint and that voice will be silenced.[Vincent Van Gogh]</item>
        <item>There is only one way to avoid criticism: do nothing, say nothing, and be nothing.[Aristotle]</item>
        <item>The only person you are destined to become is the person you decide to be.[Ralph Waldo Emerson]</item>
        <item>Everything you\'ve ever wanted is on the other side of fear.[George Addair]</item>
        <item>We can easily forgive a child who is afraid of the dark; the real tragedy of life is when men are afraid of the light.[Plato]</item>
        <item>Too many of us are not living our dreams because we are living our fears.[Les Brown]</item>
        <item>If you want to lift yourself up, lift up someone else.[Booker T. Washington]</item>
        <item>In order to succeed, your desire for success should be greater than your fear of failure.[Bill Cosby]</item>
        <item>Build your own dreams, or someone else will hire you to build theirs.[Farrah Gray]</item>
        <item>Education costs money.  But then so does ignorance.[Sir Claus Moser]</item>
        <item>Remember that not getting what you want is sometimes a wonderful stroke of luck.[Dalai Lama]</item>
        <item>You can\'t use up creativity.  The more you use, the more you have.[Maya Angelou]</item>
        <item>The only way to do great work is to love what you do.[Steve Jobs]</item>
        <item>The question isn\'t who is going to let me; it\'s who is going to stop me.[Ayn Rand]</item>
        <item>Dreaming, after all, is a form of planning.[Gloria Steinem]</item>
        <item>It\'s not what you look at that matters, it\'s what you see.[Henry David Thoreau]</item>
        <item>A day of worry is more exhausting than a week of work.[John Lubbock]</item>
        <item>Beware of false knowledge; it is more dangerous than ignorance.[George Bernard Shaw]</item>
        <item>The opinion which other people have of you is their problem, not yours.[Elisabeth Kubler-Ross]</item>
        <item>Whatever you do in life, surround yourself with smart people who\'ll argue with you.[John Wooden]</item>
        <item>Knowledge is of no value unless you put it into practice.[Anton Chekhov]</item>
        <item>Intelligence is the ability to adapt to change.[Stephen Hawking]</item>
        <item>People won\'t have time for you if you are always angry or complaining.[Stephen Hawking]</item>
        <item>However difficult life may seem, there is always something you can do and succeed at.[Stephen Hawking]</item>
        <item>We are all now connected by the Internet, like neurons in a giant brain.[Stephen Hawking]</item>
        <item>I believe alien life is quite common in the universe, although intelligent life is less so. Some say it has yet to appear on planet Earth.[Stephen Hawking]</item>
        <item>Science is not only a disciple of reason but, also, one of romance and passion.[Stephen Hawking]</item>
        <item>We love life, not because we are used to living but because we are used to loving.[Friedrich Nietzsche]</item>
        <item>Whoever fights monsters should see to it that in the process he does not become a monster. And if you gaze long enough into an abyss, the abyss will gaze back into you.[Friedrich Nietzsche]</item>
        <item>Without music, life would be a mistake.[Friedrich Nietzsche]</item>
        <item>All things are subject to interpretation whichever interpretation prevails at a given time is a function of power and not truth.[Friedrich Nietzsche]</item>
        <item>He who has a why to live can bear almost any how.[Friedrich Nietzsche]</item>
        <item>In individuals, insanity is rare; but in groups, parties, nations and epochs, it is the rule.[Friedrich Nietzsche]</item>
        <item>Thoughts are the shadows of our feelings - always darker, emptier and simpler.[Friedrich Nietzsche]</item>
        <item>There is always some madness in love. But there is also always some reason in madness.[Friedrich Nietzsche]</item>
        <item>A casual stroll through the lunatic asylum shows that faith does not prove anything.[Friedrich Nietzsche]</item>
        <item>The true man wants two things: danger and play. For that reason he wants woman, as the most dangerous plaything.[Friedrich Nietzsche]</item>
        <item>It is not a lack of love, but a lack of friendship that makes unhappy marriages.[Friedrich Nietzsche]</item>
        <item>The most common lie is that which one lies to himself; lying to others is relatively an exception.[Friedrich Nietzsche]</item>
        <item>We should consider every day lost on which we have not danced at least once. And we should call every truth false which was not accompanied by at least one laugh.[Friedrich Nietzsche]</item>
        <item>It is not when truth is dirty, but when it is shallow, that the lover of knowledge is reluctant to step into its waters.[Friedrich Nietzsche]</item>
        <item>There is more wisdom in your body than in your deepest philosophy.[Friedrich Nietzsche]</item>
        <item>In heaven, all the interesting people are missing.[Friedrich Nietzsche]</item>
        <item>Fear is the mother of morality.[Friedrich Nietzsche]</item>
        <item>Whatever is done for love always occurs beyond good and evil.[Friedrich Nietzsche]</item>
        <item>Those who cannot understand how to put their thoughts on ice should not enter into the heat of debate.[Friedrich Nietzsche]</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>